Oh, I'm falling through a hypercube I wonder what I'm doing
Think I need a hobby What's the point of doing nothing all the time?
These hypercubes are filling up my dreams It's becoming lucid
Starting to enjoy it Now I'm meeting creatures that are not of this world
Do I say hello to them? Or should I just ignore?
Maybe I should fight them Or I could just tame them
What should I do? How should I know?
I just wanna know How to greet them
In this plane of reality We're just prisoners of matter
You think we're meant for more Than what we can imagine
What if these creatures Exist beyond our dimension?
And I'm the one trespassing In this universe, it's an infinite cycle
That never ends
Do I say hello to them? Or should I just ignore?
Maybe I should fight them Or I could just tame them
What should I do? How should I know?
I just wanna know How to greet them
In this plane of reality Do I say hello to them? Or should I just ignore?
Maybe I should fight them Or I could just tame them
What should I do? How should I know?
I just wanna know How to greet them
In this plane of reality We're just prisoners of matter
You think we're meant for more Than what we can imagine
What if these creatures Exist beyond our dimension?
And I'm the one trespassing In this universe, it's an infinite cycle
That never ends